(Bernadette:)What kind of revenge is that?
(Bernadette:)This woman screwed with my job.
She's got to pay.
(Penny:)Okay, all right, honey,
you know what?
(Penny:)There was something I was too
scared to tell you yesterday,
a-and now... I'm just balls-out
terrified to tell you, but...
(Penny:)the truth is it...
(Penny:)wasn't Barbara Chen, it was me.
(Penny:)I'm the reason everyone knows.
(Bernadette:)Why did you do that?
(Penny:)Well, it was an accident.
I am so sorry I lied.
(Bernadette:)Get out.
(Penny:)Oh, you know, I also lied
about the girl in the bathroom.
(Penny:)Yeah, we actually dumped
her retainer in the toilet
(Penny:)and put it back in her mouth.
(Sheldon:)I don't understand why
I can't talk at this meeting.
'Cause when you talk,
it enrages people.
(Sheldon:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Quick question.
(Sheldon:)Am I allowed
to exchange pleasantries